Today is day two of the Bridesmaid Proposal series.
A series where I show you unique Bridesmaid Proposal gift ideas that aren't full of a bunch of junk they're gonna throw away anyways, and are budget friendly.
Today we're going with like a disco cowgirl theme.
Think Nashville Bachelor at party.
We're putting together a cute little cocktail kit.
This is me taking everything out of the box because I forgot to put cute tool in there to jush up the inside.
And crime against humanity, I know.
I threw in these cute craft mix drink packets, but obviously you can put in whatever cocktail mix suits your fancy.
I added a little card that's gonna match the front of the box, and then is that shot glass?
Not the cutest thing you've ever seen.
I mean, come on. Are you freaking kidding me?
Then the kit comes with these cute custom Bridesmaid Proposal stickers, so I'm adding one of those to the front window.
I love it because it still gives off that really personalized look that you see on like Etsy and Pinterest, but it's not a million dollars.
Then we're finally bringing back the JoJo Siwa approved giant tool bow for the front.
I layered two types of pink and white to make it super fluffy and obnoxious, and then hot glued that puppy onto the front of the box.
Of course, we had to drive the theme home with a matching pink vodka bottle, and look how freaking cute this turned out.
So unique, I'm obsessed.